So I haven't been out to see y'all in a while.
I haven't been on the road in a while.
But now that my book, What Would the Ancestors Say, is complete, I am hitting the streets.
So you can, of course, get your tickets to watch the live stream performance on November 8th and also get a signed book.
However, I will also be coming to a city near you.
And the first look of the tour is happening.
So I will see you in San Diego.
I will see you in Los Angeles.
I will see you in Seattle.
I will see you in Detroit.
I will see you in Chicago.
So come on out.
Go to AmandaSeals.com and sign up.
And, you know, let's sign some books and read some excerpts and have a good old time.
Sister Seals.
This is your ancestor.
Harriet Tubman.